earthmamaangelbaby.com 2004-06-03

# Earth Mama Angel Baby Privacy Policy

| 

**  
** Earth Mama Angel Baby™ has written this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We use your Personal Information to help you quickly find goods, services or information on the site. We track the domains from which this site is visited and use that data to analyze for trends and statistics, and then discard it. Our site uses an order form and a birth plan for customers to request information, products and services. We collect visitor's contact information such as their email address. This information is used to send orders, information about our company, the birth plan, and to facilitate Earth Mama Angel Baby's ability to market our product.

We also collect financial information such as credit card numbers when an order is placed. Once the order email has been received and fulfilled, the financial information is deleted and the contact information is retained to determine whether improvements can be made in our products or services.

We use non-persistent cookies on our site to control shopping carts. These cookies are temporary and will be removed when you close your browser window. You can completely restrict the use of cookies on your computer by turning "cookies off" on your computer's browser. However, if you choose to do this, you will not be able to order products from Earth Mama Angel Baby's shopping cart.

Any information that we collect is never sold, rented, traded or leased to third parties.

This site contains links to other sites. Earth Mama Angel Baby™ is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other web sites.

**  
** Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information. On any page that requires you to submit personally identifiable information, you have the option at that point to deny permission for future contact. Users may revoke consent for future contact with Earth Mama Angel Baby™ at any time by sending an email message to info@earthmamaangelbaby.com. If you revoke your consent, all information we have regarding you will be erased within one month.  
We sometimes are required by court orders or other laws to divulge information about you to law enforcement authorities, to government agencies or to the court.

**  
** Users may also change or modify the information previously provided by sending an email to [support@earthmamaangelbaby.com](mailto:support@earthmamaangelbaby.com)

**  
** The security of the information that you provide to us is very important to us. Hence, we have taken several measures to protect your information. All transactions involving sensitive information, such as your credit/debit card number, are conducted using an SSL (Secure Socket Layer protocol) connection. This connection provides increased security to the information that is transmitted to our website. We will only use your credit/debit number for the processing of our payment. Other sensitive information that we may collect will not be disclosed to third parties unless we are required to do so by law.

**  
** We will post any substantive changes in this privacy policy at least 30 days prior to the change taking effect. Any information collected under this current policy will remain bound by the terms of this privacy policy. After the changes take effect, all new information collected, if any, will be subject to the revised privacy policy.

If you have questions about this policy please contact us at [support@earthmamaangelbaby.com](mailto:support@earthmamaangelbaby.com) or write:

Customer Service  
Earth Mama Angel BabyTM  
3959 SW Halcyon Road  
Tualatin, OR 97062

We consider any information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally as personally identifiable information, but is not limited to:

  1. Your name 
  2. Your address 
  3. Your email address 
  4. Bank account information 
  5. Credit card information 
  6. Any combination of data that could be used to identify you such as your due date, zip code, name of your health care provider or birth plan preferences
